Ariana Kobre

9743674492 · rajdeesha@gmail.com · www.andreykurenkov.com

SUMMARY

Data scientist with strong math background and 3+ years of experience using predictive modeling, data processing and data mining algorithms to solve challenging business problems. Involved in the python open source community and passionate about deep reinforcement learning.

SKILLS

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint) Six Sigma (Black Belts) Information Technology Delivery methods PHP, Python, HTML, CSS Minitab, SPSS, Machine Learning, Tableau, My SQL

EDUCATION

Coral springs University, California September 2018 - August 2020

- M.S. in Computer Science with focus in AI
- **GPA**: CS 4.70

Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta August 2013 – May 2017

- **Dual major**: B.E. in Computer Science Engineering, B.S. in Computer Science with Research Option
- **GPA**: CS 3.0 , Overall 2.88
- Awards: Georgia Tech's President's Undergraduate Research Award

GRE: quantitative 170/170 (98th percentile), verbal 168/170 (98th percentile), writing 5.0/6.0 (93rd percentile)

MOOC: Udacity - Data Analyst Nanodegree, Coursera – Neural Networks, Machine Learning, Programming Languages, IBM data science

EXPERIENCE

DATA SCIENTIST

Google. • 2020-2021

Developed insights into the performance of Network/Studio programs and their competitors across all platforms (including linear, multiplatform and SVOD)

DATA SCIENTIST

IBM • 2021-present

Built and defined strategies for R&D data analytics.